Right now, at whatever part of your body you are having pain, place your hand there!
Viewers all over the world, those under the influence of my voice, you are included!
Place your hand right now anywhere you have that pain, affliction and infirmity.
I command that pain to leave you, in Jesus' name!
You sickness, disease, cancer, fibroid, diabetes, hypertension, tumour -
whatever it is that is a product of satan in your body, get out!
Out!
Right now, command that sickness to get out!
Command it right now!
Your body is a temple of the Holy Spirit, not a temple of sickness or disease.
Command that affliction to get out of you right now!
Command it, in the name of Jesus Christ!
I command healing in your organs, in the name of Jesus!
I command healing in your bones, in the name of Jesus!
I command healing to every part of your body, in the name of Jesus!
Be healed!
Oluwarotimi Olajide Festus from Ondo, Nigeria.
The problem which I had, had been with me for five years.
As the Mass Prayer was going on, I felt that something wanted to come out of my mouth.
Then, I vomited it and my body felt free; help me to thank God.
Strange Meatlike Object
Vomited During The Mass Prayer
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
That is what I vomited out.
It looks like meat; it is not easy to describe.
I am very surprised that such a thing can come out of me; I have never seen such a thing in my life.
We have just listened to Mr Titus Oluwarotimi.
He said he is from Ondo State.
He came with a problem of moving object that had been tormenting him for the past five years.
And he said when the mass prayer was going on, the Spirit of God touched him
and he felt like vomiting.
He was struggling; something wanted to come out of his system.
When that thing came out, he vomited this object we are seeing right in front of him.
You can see how the object looks like. We can't really give a description of what it is.
He said this is what had been tormenting him for so long.
After vomiting this object we are seeing, he can now press his stomach without pain,
he can breathe without pain. All that pain is gone now and he is completely free
from this problem that had been moving in his body and tormenting him for the past five years.
He said he vomited this out of his stomach because the thing continued to move
all around his stomach - from one part to another. But today, he has been set free.
TESTIMONY TIME
That was how it all happened.
The man who was set free during the mass prayer is going to speak in one of the Nigerian languages
and we are going to interpret for us in English.
Testimony Time
Mr Oluwarotimi Olajide Festus
Ondo, Nigeria
The man said his name is Mr Oluwarotimi Olajide Festus, and he is from Ondo State (Nigeria).
I thank God that I came to The SCOAN.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was moving objects all over m body
and I had this problem for five years.
I went to many witch doctors and medical practitioners but there was no solution.
He said he came to The SCOAN with the problem of severe moving object for five years.
He went to several places in search of solution to this problem of severe moving object
We want to ask him more, how God Almighty set him free from this problem.
Mr Oluwarotimi Olajide Festus
Mass Prayer Testimony
The object was moving all over my body and as a result, I was not okay.
I emitted a bad smell anytime I belched.
It was as if I was in a cage and I felt so uneasy.
I then decided to come to The SCOAN.
The man further explained that this problem had been tormenting him for the past five years.
The problem of severe moving object gave him discomfort all over his body
because the object kept on moving from one part of his body to another.
Because of this problem, he developed a body odour; he smelt like a rotten meat.
This had been the problem he had been nursing, moving from one place to another
but there was no solution before he came to The SCOAN.
Mr Oluwarotimi Olajide Festus
Mass Prayer Testimony
I thank God Almighty. When they were conducting the Mass Prayer that Sunday,
it was as if hot water was poured on me.
Suddenly, I vomited and my body became light.
I was surprised that that substance actually came out of my body.
My body became light.
Since that Sunday, everything has been going fine for me.
The man further explained that God Almighty set him free when he came to The SCOAN.
During the Mass Prayer, when the evangelists were praying,
he felt like a hot water was poured on him and his body started shaking and shivering.
He felt like vomiting, something wanted to come out of him.
He intended to run out but he was asked to go back inside the church.
As he was there shivering, he wanted to vomit, something wanted to come out of him forcefully.
When that thing came out, it was that substance like a raw meat
that we saw on the floor a moment ago and it is on the screen right now.
This is what he vomited out.
He said, since he vomited this raw meat substance, all the pain, discomfort,
the excessive sweating and body odour are gone.
That he is completely free now, and he is here to thank God Almighty for what God has done for him.
So, we want to ask him more questions regarding this problem.
We want him to tell us how he came about this very problem in his life.
Mr Oluwarotimi Olajide Festus
Mass Prayer Testimony
I had this problem when I went to a witch doctor who gave me charms to eat
because I was in need of a career breakthrough as a technician and driver.
I first worked as a technician and during this time, I went to a witch doctor
and my life was totally destroyed.
Then, I became a driver and at a point, I owned eight buses and a car.
After visiting a witch doctor, I sold all my vehicles
and I could not give account of the money realised from the sales.
I wondered what could be happening to me so, I decided that I must come to The SCOAN.
That was how I came last week Sunday.
I went to the witch doctor because I wanted a breakthrough in my career.
When I visited the witch doctor, my problems became worse.
I started blaming myself.
The witch doctor prepared a charm with snail and meat for me to eat.
Since I was given the charm to eat,
I started experiencing moving objects all over my body and things became bad for me.
We further asked the man what the cause was for this problem of severe moving object in his life.
He said, the problem started when he visited a witch doctor.
He visited a witch doctor and asked the witch doctor to do a charm for him
so that he could progress in all his endeavours.
He said the witch doctor did a lot of concoctions and cooked a lot of things
like snails and other forms of animals and put everything together
and asked him to eat. After he ate that, he later found out
that something started moving all around his body, giving him discomfort.
Not only was he afflicted at that point in time,
he said the things he had before he went to the witch doctor -
he had eight buses and one car - they were all gone.
They were all completely destroyed. He lost everything and became poor after he visited the witch doctor.
This problem of moving object also started, giving him discomfort.
He had to move from one place to another and this is how he had been suffering for five years
before he visited The SCOAN.
Last week Sunday he vomited out a raw meat substance
and ever since then, he has been completely free.
Shall we put our hands together for the miracle-working Jesus!
Mr Oluwarotimi Olajide Festus
Mass Prayer Testimony
My body is light and totally different from the way it was since last Sunday.
I do see the man of God in my dream now.
Around 12am today, I saw the man of God in my dream.
He then gave me the keys of a brand new vehicle and house.
He told me that I should fear not, that my security is guaranteed. This gave me confidence.
We give glory to God. The man further explained that he is giving thanks to God Almighty.
That ever since he vomited that raw meat substance, he has been very free
and he has also been having dreams of the man of God, coming to pray for him in his dreams.
That even last night, he saw the man of God coming to him in his dream,
handing over to him his breakthrough keys
and telling him that he should not be afraid, that God will continue to be with him and secure him.
Mr Oluwarotimi Olajide Festus
Mass Prayer Testimony
My advice to everyone is to move close to God.
We asked him what his word of advice is for everyone listening
and the man said that he wants everyone to trust in God Almighty.
Mr Oluwarotimi Olajide Festus
Mass Prayer Testimony
We encouraging him that now, that the Lord God Almighty in His infinite mercy
has set him free - not only setting him free, healing him and delivering him from that problem -
that he should make the Word of God the standard for his life, keep the Word in his heart
and see to it that he does what the Word says and we pray that God Almighty will grant him
the inner grace to do so, in Jesus' name.
Once again, shall we put our hands together for the miracle-working Jesus!
We want to listen to more testimonies from the man that vomited a raw meat substance
during the Mass Prayer offered by the evangelists sent by the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Join us as we listen to him. He is going to speak in one of the Nigerian languages,
and we are going to interpret for us in English.
Mr Oluwarotimi Olajide Festus.
I was the person that vomited a meat-like substance during the Mass Prayer.
Since I vomited that meat-like substance, I am healed.
All the things I used to experience before are gone.
I no longer experience the body pains and hotness. I thank God.
We have listened to the man. He said his name is Mr Oluwarotimi Olajide Festus from Ondo State.
He is the very man that vomited a raw-meat substance
during the course of the Mass Prayer offered by the evangelists.
He said, before he vomited that raw-meat substance,
he was having severe stomach pain and hotness of the body -
that is, internal heat and a lot of discomfort.
After he vomited that raw-meat substance, all the pains are gone; he is no longer having the pain.
He can press his stomach now without pain, and he is not feeling any discomfort.
He is very happy that God Almighty has set him free from all forms of pain
that came as a result of that raw-meat substance that was in his system, that he vomited out.
He is so thankful to God Almighty for setting him free.
We also want to let him know that the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua rejoices with him
for what God Almighty has done in his life and sent to him this cash gift of 150,000 Naira
to support him and to let him know that Jesus loves and cares for him.
Mr Oluwarotimi Festus Receives 150,000 Naira
From Prophet T.B. Joshua & Emmanuel TV Partners
I thank God for this blessing He has given me through Prophet T.B. Joshua.
God will continue to uphold him and Emmanuel TV Partners.
We have listened to Mr Oluwarotimi, thanking God Almighty
for what God has done in his life through the Mass Prayer offered by the evangelists
and the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua and the entire Emmanuel TV Partners sending to him
the cash gift of 150,000 Naira to support him.
He said that he is so thankful and so grateful to all of them for this cash gift
that was sent to him and he is so happy.
He will continue to serve God, continue to walk in the way of the Lord.
We pray that God Almighty will grant him the inner grace to do so, in Jesus' name.
I thank God Almighty!